&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，希望我们对词法范围感觉很好。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so hopefully we're feeling pretty good about lexical scope.
但是，让我们测试一下其中存在的一些小边缘和拐角情况。
But let's test some of the little edges and corner cases that exist within this.
让我们确保我们的理解是完全有效的。
Let's make sure our understanding is fully working.
所以，我们将以与上一张幻灯片完全相同的方式处理这个问题，
So, we're gonna process this exactly the same way as we did on the previous slide,
那就是我们想先做编译，然后再执行。
which is that we want to first do the compilation, and then do the execution.
既然你现在都是专家并获得了这方面的认证
Since you're now all experts and certified in this I'm gonna expect
你要能够跟我一起大声说出所有这些事情。
you to be able to follow along and say out loud with me all of these things.
因此，处理开始于编译器与作用域管理器的对话。
So processing begins with the compiler talking to the scope manager.
编译器在第一行说，嘿，范围管理器。
And compiler says on line one, hey scope manager.
嘿全球范围，我有一个，什么样的参考？
Hey global scope, I have a, what kind of reference?
我有一个正式的声明，在执行中它将是一个目标引用，但是，
I have a formal declaration, in execution it will be a target reference but,
在我的编辑过程中，我有一个正式的
during my compilation I have a formal
申报
declaration for
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：教师&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：教师。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Teacher &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Teacher.
听说过吗？
Ever heard of it?
答案是
And the answer is
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没有，没听说过。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: No, haven't heard of it.
这是在编译阶段。
This is in compilation stage.
我们将在执行中听说它。
We will of heard of it in execution.
在编译阶段，我们从未听说过它。
In compilation stage we'd never heard of it.
所以我们继续创造什么样的大理石？
So we go ahead and create what kind of marble?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：红色。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是你的红色
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Red. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your red
大理石，好吗？
marble, okay?
然后我们把红色的球，砰的一声，直接扔进红色的桶里。
And we drop the red ball, boop, directly into the red bucket.
现在我们在哪一行找到下一个正式声明？
Now we find the next formal declaration on what line?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：3。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Three.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第三行。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line three.
我们有正式的声明。
We have the formal declaration.
嘿全局作用域正式声明为一个标识符调用。
Hey global scope formal declaration for an identifier called.
其他类。其他班级，听说过吗？
OtherClass. OtherClass, ever heard of it?
答案是？
And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：从未听说过。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Never heard of it.
太好了，所以我们需要什么？
Great, so we need a what?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：红色大理石。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Red marble. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Red marble.
这是你的红色大理石，砰，放在红色的桶里。
Here's your red marble, boop, goes in the red bucket.
顺便说一下，全局范围，这是一个函数。
By the way, global scope, that's a function.
它需要自己的桶。
It needs its own bucket.
你能给我做一个蓝色的桶吗？
Can you make me a blue bucket?
当然，我们做了一个蓝色的桶。
Sure, we make a blue bucket.
这是你的蓝色水桶，现在我们进入这个范围，
Here is your blue bucket and now we step into that scope and
我们处理它的计划，或者我们制定它的计划。
we process its plan, or we make it's plan.
那么我们找到的下一个正式声明在哪里呢？
So where is the next formal declaration that we find?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：第四行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Line four.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：9。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Nine.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：等一下。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Wait a minute.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第四行是正式声明吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Is line four a formal declaration?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没有var。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There's no var there.
那第五行呢，这是正式声明吗？
What about line five, is that a formal declaration?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么第六行呢，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What about line six,
正式声明？
formal declaration?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们没有制造任何蓝色的弹珠，是吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We don't make any blue marbles, do we?
好的，记住这一点。
Okay, so keep that in mind.
你可能想知道第五行会发生什么，而且
You may be wondering what's gonna happen with line five, and
我们将在执行过程中讨论这一点，但从编译器的角度来看，
we'll talk about that during execution, but from the perspective of the compiler,
我们没有任何正式的声明，所以没有要创建的弹珠。
we didn't have any formal declarations, so there's no marbles to create.
好的，我们已经完成了蓝色桶的工作。
Okay so we're done with the blue bucket.
实际上它是存在的，但实际上它里面没有弹珠。
Effectively it exists, but effectively it has no marbles in it.
我们退回到全局范围。
We step back out to the global scope.
我们在这个程序中找到了更多的正式声明吗？
Do we find anymore formal declarations in this program?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我们完成了编译。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we're done with compilation.
拇指向上，拇指向下，我们感觉如何？
Thumbs up, thumbs down, how do we feel?
好的，和以前一样。
Okay, same process as before.
我正在努力训练你，让你的头脑中有这样的故事，即使
And I'm trying to train you to have that narrative in your head even if
研讨会结束后，你再也不会大声说出这些话了。
you never say the words out loud ever again after this workshop.
我要你在脑海里思考这个故事。
I want you to think that narrative in your head.
思考正在发生的问题和答案，因为这涉及到
Think about the question and answering that is happening because that talks about
或者说明在编译器和作用域计划之间发生的交换。
or illustrates the interchange that occurs between the compiler and the scope plan.
这就是你如何理解示波器的工作原理，
That's how you understand how scopes work,
就是当你了解它们是如何被设置的，以及它们是如何被使用的，好吗？
is when you understand how they get set up, and how they get used, okay?
现在，让我们执行这段代码。
So now, let's execute this code.
它的执行方式与我们在上一张幻灯片中所做的完全相同。
It executes exactly the same way as we would have, done in the previous slide.
所以我们记住，没有正式的声明，但是
So we remember, there's no formal declarations but
有可执行的语句。
there are executable statements.
第一行有一个可执行语句。
Line one has an executable statement.
所以我们就是引擎
And so we are the engine and
我们说，嘿，全球范围，我有。什么样的引用？
we say, hey, global scope, I have a.what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：目标。&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我有一个目标引用
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Target. &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a target reference
给老师的。
for teacher.
听说过吗？
Ever heard of it?
答案是，&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
And the answer is, &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没有。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Nope. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your red marble.
是的，是的。
Yes, right yes.
这是你的什么颜色的大理石？
Here’s your what color marble?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：红色。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Red.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here’s your red marble.
很好，我们引用Kyle的价值，我们将其分配到红色大理石中，然后
Great, we take the value quote Kyle, we assign it into the red marble, and
我们完成了。
we are complete.
大家都同意吗？
Everybody good with that?
好吧。
All right.
现在请记住，函数是声明，它们实际上并不存在。
Now remember, functions are declarations, they don't really exist.
至少，他们只是象征性地在这里。
At least, they're only here symbolically.
所以我们将从这个函数移到下一个执行代码行，
So we're going to move from the function to the next execution line of code,
那就是九号线。
which would be line nine.
第九行是如何执行的？
How does line nine execute?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：嘿，全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Hey global scope.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，全球范围，那是红色的桶。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey global scope, that's the red bucket.
嘿全球范围我这里有什么样的参考？
Hey global scope I have what kind of reference here?
我在九号线上有什么样的推荐人？
What kind of reference do I have on line nine?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：来源。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：源引用，我有一个源引用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Source reference, I have a source reference for
称为其他类的标识符。
an identifier called other class.
你以前听说过他吗？
Have you ever heard of him before?
答案是？
And the answer is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes, here's your red marble.
凯尔·辛普森：这是你的红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your red marble.
谢谢，你学到了。
Thanks, you're picking up on it.
好的，这是你的红色大理石，好吗？
Right, here's your red marble, okay?
我知道这听起来很傻。
I know it sounds silly.
但它可以帮助你处理本来很干燥的东西
But it helps you process what would otherwise be a really dry and
无聊的话题。
boring topic.
所以，跟着我，好吗。
So, just stick with me, all right.
这是你的红色大理石。
Here's your red marble.
那么，我们在那个红色大理石里发现了什么？
So, what do we find in that red marble?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：参考。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A reference.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：对我们调用的函数的引用
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A reference to the function which we've called
这里的other Class附加了这个蓝色的作用域桶。
otherClass here which has attached to it this blue bucket of scope.
所以我们找到这个函数，在第九行用括号执行它，然后
So we find that function, we execute it with the parenthesis on line nine, and
行刑移动到哪一条线？
execution moves to what line?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：4。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Four.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第四行，第四行如何执行？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line four, how does line four execute?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：嘿，蓝桶。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Hey, blue bucket.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，蓝桶，我有一个，什么样的推荐人？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey, blue bucket, I have a, what kind of reference?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：来源。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我有一个目标引用，因为它正在接收任务。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a target reference because it is receiving an assignment.
我有一个老师的目标参考。
I have a target reference for teacher.
听说过吗，答案是？
Ever heard of it, and the answer is?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：那么我们去哪里？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So where do we go?
上一个。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：向上一。
One up. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Up one.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嘿，全球范围，我有一个目标参考
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey, global scope, I have a target reference for
老师没听说过。
teacher ever heard of it.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yes.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这是你的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Here's your.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：红色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Red marble.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：重要的是要看到这里是红色大理石，而不是蓝色大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Important to see that it's a red marble here not a blue marble.
即使我们在蓝色范围内，我们引用的是红色大理石。
Even though we're inside of the blue scope, we are referencing a red marble.
你和我一起吗？
You with me?
所以我们得到了一个红色的大理石，当我们将Suzy的报价分配给它时，
So we get a red marble and when we assign quote Suzy to it,
我们正在对当前存在的值进行赋值，
we are assigning over the value that was currently there,
引用凯尔的话，因为这个案子里的大理石是一样的。
the quote Kyle, because it's the same marble in this case.
这没有被遮蔽，因为我们没有在另一个类中声明教师
This wasn't shadowed because we didn't declare teacher inside of the otherClass
功能。
function.